Personal papers of Desmond McCarthy
World Bank Group Archives
- Quality Assurance Group (QAG) review and assessment, 1997 - 2005; WB IBRD/IDA WB_IBRD/IDA_112-03; 1.63 linear feet of textual records
  * See Records of the Europe and Central Asia Regional Vice Presidency ([WB IBRD/IDA ECA](https://archivesholdings.worldbank.org/records-of-europe-and-central-asia-regional-vice-presidency) for records related to lending operations in Bulgaria.
  - Country Analytical and Advisory Assistance - Bulgaria - National Energy Efficiency Study - P079044, 2002-06-11 - ?; 30295863
  - Country Analytical and Advisory Assistance - Bulgaria - Public Expenditure Issues - P071564, 2000-09-01 - ?; 30295862
  - Country Analytical and Advisory Assistance - Bulgaria - Country Procurement Assessment Report - P084316, 2004-06-11 - ?; 30295865
  - Poverty - Bulgaria, 2001-10-29 - ?; 30295864
  - Non Lending Technical Assistance -Documentation - China - Services - Secretary - Census - P083267, 2003-01-22 - 2005-03-17; 30295868
  - Country Analytical and Advisory Assistance - Bulgaria - Rural Development Assessment - P079215, 2004-04-01 - ?; 30295861
  - Country Analytical and Advisory Assistance - Lebanon - Poverty Survey - Technical assistance - P079419, 1997-11-07 - 2004-09-22; 30295867
  - Quality assurance group - Assessment of Customs Modernization Handbook, 2004-11-30 - 2005-10-04; 30295869
  - Non technical lending assistance - Documentation - Romania - State - Owned Bank technical assistance, 2002-09-01 - 2004-06-29; 30295866